adsupply.com 2014-12-18

# AdSupply - Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for AdSupply. AdSupply is committed to protecting your privacy online. Please read the information below to learn the following regarding your use of this site.

**What information do we collect?**

Our primary goal in collecting information from our users is to provide them with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience while using member sites. In order to better protect our users’ privacy online, we collect only one type of information about our users: Non-Personally Identifiable Information; we do not collect any Personally Identifiable Information about you, nor do we collect or identify your browsing habits. Non-Personally Identifiable Information refers to information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. We gather certain information about our users based upon where they visit on member sites in several ways. This information is compiled and analyzed on both a personal and an aggregated basis. 

**What do we use your information for?**

We do not sell, trade, rent or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We actively encourage our service partners to adopt and post privacy policies. However, the use of your Personally Identifiable Information by our service partners is governed by the privacy policies of those service partners, and is not subject to our control. Non-Personally Identifiable Information may be provided to other parties for, among other uses, marketing and/or advertising.

Occasionally we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide Personally Identifiable Information to the appropriate governmental authorities. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information upon receipt of a court order, subpoena, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful.

We may also provide Non-Personally Identifiable Information about our customers to third party advertisers, but these statistics do not include any Personally Identifiable Information.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes. As a third party vendor, AdSupply participates in passive information collection, and may store cookies to facilitate and customize your user experience on member sites. A cookie is a small data text file that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. Our cookies store randomly assigned user identification numbers and the country where you are located. No Personally Identifiable Information is collected. All information shared with advertisers is anonymous. These cookies makes a user experience on the site easier, makes the site run more smoothly and helps us to maintain a secure site. 

AdSupply’s cookies enable AdSupply to serve advertisements to users based on their visits to these sites utilizing our technology. AdSupply uses cookies to keep track of advertisements and to report to the advertiser if you have seen a particular advertisement and clicked or acted on that advertisement only. These cookies are used to control how many advertisements are seen during a user’s time on this site. AdSupply does not track activity across multiple sites. Blocking or removing these cookies may cause more advertisements than the partner site intended. 

**Security of Information**

We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to guard your personally identifiable information. We allow access to personal information only to persons engaging in activity provided for by this Privacy Policy. We use secure socket layer technology, among other technologies, to protect any credit card information provided to us.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personally Identifiable Information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; (b) the security, integrity and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this site cannot be guaranteed; and (c) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party.

**User Choices on Collection and Use of Information**

You also have choices with respect to cookies, as described above. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies, some parts of our site and/or member sites may not work properly in your case.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your Personally Identifiable Information to outside parties without your express consent.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

AdSupply is in complete compliance with the requirements of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) and the compliance Rule adopted by the FTC with respect thereto. AdSupply does not collect any information from anyone under thirteen (13) years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least thirteen (13) years old or older. You must be at least thirteen (13) years old to have our permission to use this site.

**Third-Party Sites**

Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. Other sites accessible through our site have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. Please consult each site's privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties. Additionally, other companies which place advertising on our site may collect information about you when you view or click on their advertising through the use of cookies. We cannot control this collection of information. You should contact these advertisers directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect. This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website. Our Terms and Conditions can be found at <http://adsupply.com/advertisers.html> and <http://adsupply.com/publishers.html>.

**Your Consent**

You acknowledge that this Privacy Policy is part of our Site Terms of Use, and by accessing or using our site, you agree to be bound by all of its terms and conditions. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Such changes, modifications, additions or deletions shall be effective immediately upon notice thereof, which may be given by means including, but not limited to, issuing an email and/or posting the revised Policy on this page. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this site and this Policy periodically and to be aware of any modifications. Your continued use of the site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by the modified Policy.

_This policy was last modified on April 24, 2013._

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us by sending a letter to:

**10811 Washington Blvd, Suite 400  
Culver City, CA 90232  
info@adsupply.com  
**

_This Privacy Policy is powered by Trust Guard PCI compliance._
